[
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If she hadn't told him, he ____.",
			"optionA":"would have never found out",
			"optionB":"will never find out",
			"optionC":"would never find out",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"I ____ this if you hadn't asked me.",
			"optionA":"didn't do",
			"optionB":"would never have done",
			"optionC":"wouldn't do",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If I ____ about this, I would have told you.",
			"optionA":"know",
			"optionB":"knew",
			"optionC":"had known",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If they ____ to rest they would not have been so tired.",
			"optionA":"had stopped",
			"optionB":"have stopped",
			"optionC":"didn't stop",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"I ____ that he's 38 years old if he hadn't told me.",
			"optionA":"would never guess",
			"optionB":"wouldn't have guessed",
			"optionC":"didn't guess",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If I hadn't seen that movie, I ____ to see it with you.",
			"optionA":"would go",
			"optionB":"would gone",
			"optionC":"would have gone",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If you ____ the money that you owe me, I would have asked you.",
			"optionA":"had returned",
			"optionB":"returned",
			"optionC":"have returned",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"Thomas wouldn't have bought the jacket if it ____ on sale.",
			"optionA":"wasn't",
			"optionB":"hadn't been",
			"optionC":"wouldn't be",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If you ____ me, I wouldn't have known about the party.",
			"optionA":"haven't called",
			"optionB":"didn't call",
			"optionC":"hadn't called",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"Tina would have called you if you ____ her your number.",
			"optionA":"had given",
			"optionB":"would give",
			"optionC":"didn't give",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If they hadn't been drunk, the doorman ____.",
			"optionA":"has let them in",
			"optionB":"would have let them in",
			"optionC":"had let them in",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If you ____ your last exam, you would have graduated in May.",
			"optionA":"wouldn't have failed",
			"optionB":"hadn't failed",
			"optionC":"have not failed",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"She ____ this apartment if she had known it was so noisy.",
			"optionA":"wouldn't have rented",
			"optionB":"did not rent",
			"optionC":"had rented",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"I would not ____ to see this movie if I had known how boring it was.",
			"optionA":"go",
			"optionB":"have gone",
			"optionC":"had gone",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If I hadn't lost my cellphone, I ____ you.",
			"optionA":"had called",
			"optionB":"would call",
			"optionC":"would have called",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If I hadn't driven so fast, I ____ into an accident.",
			"optionA":"would not have gotten",
			"optionB":"would not get",
			"optionC":"hadn't gotten",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If the store ____ open, I would have bought some food.",
			"optionA":"would be",
			"optionB":"had been",
			"optionC":"was",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"I ____ on time if I hadn't missed the bus.",
			"optionA":"had been",
			"optionB":"have been",
			"optionC":"would have been",
			"rightOption":"c"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If you hadn't changed your hairstyle, I ____ you.",
			"optionA":"would have recognized",
			"optionB":"had recognized",
			"optionC":"would recognize",
			"rightOption":"a"
		}
	},
	{
	"task":
		{
			"prompt":"If I ____ full, I would have eaten more.",
			"optionA":"would not have been",
			"optionB":"hadn't been",
			"optionC":"would be",
			"rightOption":"b"
		}
	}
]